Guide to the Doris Duke American Indian oral history project audio recordings 1949-1972
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
- Philip Johnston, John D. Sylvester, 1970 November 07; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 954)
- Jimmy Yazzie, Ida Mae Yazzie, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 955-I)
- Jimmy Yazzie, Ida Mae Yazzie, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 955-II)
- Maggie Holgate (Navajo), undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 956-I)
  Navajo Mountain.
- Maggie Holgate (Navajo), undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 956-II)
- Grey Eyes, Irene Stuart, Dave Gorman, 1968 May 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 957-I)
  Translation of original interview by Benjamin Lee.
- Grey Eyes, Irene Stuart, Dave Gorman, 1968 May 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 957-II)
- Harry Price, Tona Lue (Navajo), 1965 July 06; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 958-I)
- Harry Price, Tona Lue (Navajo), 1965 July 06; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 958-II)
- Grandma Benally (Navajo), 1968 May 04; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 959-I)
- Grandma Benally (Navajo), 1968 May 04; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 959-II)
- Irene Stuart, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 960)
  Canyon De Chelly
  Tracks 1&2 are translation, Tracks 3&4 are original interview.
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 18 minutes.
- Harry Price, Grandma Benally (Navajo), 1964 October 21; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 961-I)
  Canyon De Chelly.
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 41 minutes.
- Frank Mitchell, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 961-II)
- Harry Price, Grandma Benally (Navajo), undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 962-I)
  Canyon De Chelly-Selections One through Three.
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 36 minutes.
- Harry Price, Grandma Benally (Navajo), undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 962-II)
- Harry Price, Grandma Benally (Navajo), undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 963)
  Canyon De Chelly-Selections three and four.
  2 reel-to-reel audiotapes.
- Grey Eyes, 1965 July 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 964)
- Frank Mitchell, 1965 July 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 965)
  3 reel-to-reel audiotapes
- Grey Eyes, 1965 June 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 966)
- Frank Mitchell, 1965 July 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 967)
- Tonahue Price, Harry Price, Danny Yazzie (Navajo), 1965 June 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 968)
- Joe Cap (Navajo), 1968 June 24; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 969)
- Grandma Johnson (Navajo), undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 970)
- Grandma Benally, Joe Brown (Navajo), undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 971)
  Canyon De Chelly-Selections five and six.
- Grandma Benally, Terry Christ (Navajo, Ute/Apache ?), 1964 November 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 972)
  Apache, Utes, Wide Rock Huelte.
- Grandma Benally, 1964 November 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 973-I)
- Grandma Benally, Harry Price, 1964 November 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 973-II)
- Phyllis DeLos Santos (Clerk Typist), 1970 November 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 974)
  "Urbanization of the American Indian Oral History Project"
- Frank L. Haggerty Jr. (Tribal Operations Officer), 1970 November 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 975)
- Ron Pinkham (Nez Perce), 1970 November 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 976)
  Available compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 48 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Clare Engle in Santa Ana, California
- Ron Pinkham (Nez Perce), 1970 November 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 977)
- Celcelia Charley (Clerk), 1970 November 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 978)
- Miriam Sheddon, 1970 November 06; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 979)
  Available compact disc copy (4 CDs) Total running time 3 hours 13 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Clare Engle in Fullerton, California
- Mrs. Tony Stoliby (Tribal Operations Assistant), 1970 November 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 980)
- Mary Shangreau, 1970 November 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 981)
  Mary Shangreau is a realty Specialist through the Bureau of Indian Affairs. She discusses issues concerning the Urbanization of the Native American.
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 24 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Clare Engle in Riverside, California
- Danny Scott (Eskahwapkah), 1970 November 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 982)
  Interviewed and recorded by Kathy Biel
  Running Time: 2 hrs
- Dennis Clah (Navajo), 1970 November 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 983)
- John Knifechief, Lois Knifechief (President of Orange County Indian Center), 1970 October 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 984)
  Available compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 39 minutes.
- Fern Charley, 1970 February 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 985)
- Sam A. Pinto (Navajo), undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 986)
- Philip Hubbell, 1969 October 16; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 987)
  Speech before Albuquerque Historical Society.
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 12 minutes.
- Stephen S. Jones (Sioux), 1970 November 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 988)
  Peyote cults.
  Available compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 45 minutes.
- Philip Johnston, 1970 November 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 989)
- Christmas Ceremonies at Acoma Pueblo, 1970 December 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 990)
  Christmas ceremonies at the Acoma Pueblo.
  9 reel-to-reel audiotapes, compact disc copy (9 CDs) Total running time 7 hours 21 minutes.
- Recording unavailable (Reel 991)
- Lulu Brock, Natheline Santio, Conrad Reed, Marietta Reed (Ute), 1971 September; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 992)
- Alez Seotewa (Zuni), 1971 September 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 993)
  Painting murals at the Church of Guadalupe in Zuni Pueblo.
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 16 minutes.
- Katie Poblano, Sam Poblano (Zuni), 1971 September 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 994)
- B.J Vanderwagen, 1971 September 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 995)
- Sam Poblano (Zuni), 1971 September 07; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 996)
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 52 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Dr. Gregory C. Crampton
- Unknown Singer, 1969 March 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 997)
  Navajo Songs
  Recorded by David Brugge
- Recording unavailable (Reel 998)
- Anthony Purley, 1971 January; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 999)
  Interviewed and recorded by Kathy Mackay
- Clarence Turner (Paiute), 1971 January; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1000)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 50 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Tom Joseph
- Intertribal Council-Mr. Reginald Elgin, 1971 February 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1001)
  Intertribal Council.
  Interviewed by Floyd O'Neil.
- Katheleen Koskela, 1971 February 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1002)
  Native American Studies committee, University of Santa Cruz.
  Interviewed and recorded by Floyd A. O'Neil in Santa Cruz, California.
- Don Patterson, 1971 February 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1003)
  Native American Center of San Francisco.
  Interviewed and recorded by Floyd A. O'Neil in San Francisco, California
- Emmett St. Marie, 1971 January 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1004)
  Interviewed and recorded by Floyd A. O'Neil in Banning, California
- Sanford Smith (Part Ute), 1971 January 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1005)
  UCLA
  Interviewed and recorded by Floyd A. O'Neil
- Monroe Price, 1971 January 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1006)
  UCLA Law School
- Alverto Carruth, Richard M. Johnson, 1971 January 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1007)
  Interviewed and recorded by Floyd A. O'Neil in Los Angeles, California
- Mr. Dave Lester, 1971 January 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1008)
  Interviewed and recorded by Floyd A. O'Neil and Kathy MacKay in Los Angeles, California
- Joseph C. Vasquez, 1971 January 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1009)
  Native American Center of Los Angeles
  Interviewed and recorded by Floyd A. O'Neil and Kathy Mackay in Los Angeles, California.
- Elizabeth Sperline, 1971 January 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1010)
  Californian Native American Education Assessment
  Interviewed and recorded by Floyd A. O'Neil and Tom Joseph
- Jim Olquin, 1971 January 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1011)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 36 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Jim Olquin in Los Angeles, California
- Ted Boles, 1971 January 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1012)
  Native American Free Clinic
  Interviewed and recorded by J. Allen and K. MacKay in California
- Glen Whitman, 1971 February 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1013)
  Native American Center of San Jose, California
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A. O'Neil in San Jose, California.
- Robert Overacker, 1971 February 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1014)
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A. O'Neil in San Francisco
- David Risling Jr., 1971 February 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1015)
  California Indian Education Association, Inc.
  Summary of the interview.
  Interviewed and recorded by G. C. Thompson and K. MacKay
- Dan Bomberry, 1970 December 18; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1016)
  Native American urbanization.
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Long Beach, California
  Running time: 1 hour.
- Katherine Saubel, 1970 December 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1017)
  Native American urbanization
  Interviewed and recorded by Kathy Biel in Banning, California
- Emmett St. Marie, 1970 December 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1018)
- William Wiley, 1970 December 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1019)
  Interviewed and recorded by Kathy Biel in Riverside, California
- Madeline Ball, 1971 January 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1020)
- Dan Bomberry, 1970 December 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1021)
- Hotona Roebuck, 1970 December 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1022)
- Hotona Roebuck, 1970 December 17; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1023)
- Dan Bomberry, 1971 January 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1024)
  Native American Urbanization.
- Gene Pasqua, Ike Lief, 1971 July; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1025)
  Pit River
  Interviewed and recorded by T. Joseph and Jack Allen.
- Bill Franklin (Mewoc of Ione Area), 1971 February 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1026)
  Permission to use necessary from Interviewee.
  Mewoc Indians of the Ione, California Area.
  Interviewed and recorded by Jack Allen
- Henry Crow Dog (Lakota Sioux), 1971 March; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1027)
  "Crow Dog Speaks-UCLA"
  Recorded by Anthony Purley in Rose Bud, South Dakota
- Stanley D. Lyman, 1971 February 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1028)
  Interviewed and recorded by K. MacKay, F. A. O'Neil, and G. C. Thompson in Salt Lake City, Utah
- Stanley D. Lyman, 1971 February 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1029)
- Stanley D. Lyman, 1971 February 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1030)
- Stanley D. Lyman, 1971 February 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1031)
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A. O'Neil, G. C. Thompson, and K. MacKay in Salt Lake City, Utah
- George W. Woodward, 1971 March 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1032)
  Relocated Native Americans
  Interviewed and recorded by J. Kalpatrick and Gerald Huntley in Oakland, California
- George W. Woodward, 1971 March 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1033)
  Relocated Native American
  Interviewed and recorded by J. Kalpatrick, G. Huntley, and F. A. O'Neil in Oakland, California
  Tape 1033 comes before tape 1032
- John Jacobs, 1971 March 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1034)
  Friendship House Alcoholism
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A. O'Neil in San Francisco, California
- Marie Streeter, 1971 March 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1035)
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A. O'Neil in San Jose, California
- Marie Streeter, 1971 March 03; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1036)
- Mary Tom (Navajo), 1971 February 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1037)
  Interview conducted in Navajo.
  Interviewed and recorded by Benjamin Lee in Gamerco, New Mexico
- American Indian Law Students, 1971 March 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1038)
  OEO Legal Services
  First reel of the second day's readings.
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 56 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A O'Neil in Denver, Colorado.
- American Indian Law Students, 1971 March 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1039)
  American Indian Law Students Association.
  Second reel of the second day's readings.
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A O'Neil in Denver, Colorado
- American Indian Law Students, 1971 March 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1040)
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 18 minutes.
- American Indian Law Students, 1971 March 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1041)
- Kenneth Yackus (Comanche), 1970 December 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1042)
  Breakdown of blood heritage requirements to be considered a Comanche Indian, Indian Bureau in Oklahoma and the Native American in the Marine Corps.
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Garden Grove, California
- American Indian Law Students, 1971 March 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1043)
- American Indian Law Students, 1971 March 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1044)
  American Indian Law Students Association-OEO Legal Aid.
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 51 minutes.
- Recording unavailable (Reel 1045)
- American Indian Law Students, 1971 March 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1046)
- American Indian Law Students, 1971 March 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1047)
- M. Gage, 1971 March 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1048)
  Denver Employment Assistance
  Interviewed and recorded by K. MacKay and F. A. O'Neil in Denver, Colorado.
- American Indian Law Students, 1971 March 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1049)
  Interviewed and recorded by F. A O'Neil and G. C. Thompson in Denver, Colorado
- Recording unavailable (Reel 1050)
- Ted Boles, 1970 December 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1051)
  Native American Urbanization Project
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 15 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Marian Ryan in Compton, California
- Joe Myers (Pomo), 1971 April 21; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1052)
  Interviewed and recorded by J. Kilpatrick and G. Huntley in Berkeley, California
- Larry Myers (Pomo), 1971 April 21; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1053)
- Lilly Moore, 1971 January 14; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1054)
- Holly McClelland, 1970 October 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1055)
  Interviewed and recorded by Kathy Biel.
  Running Time: 50 minutes.
- John Quick, 1971 February 25; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1056)
  Alamitos Intermediate School
  Interviewed and recorded by Marian Ryan in Garden Grove, California
- Elijah Smith (Oneida), 1970 November 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1057)
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 40 minutes.
- Wallace Newman (Luisiano), 1970 November 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1058)
  Early life and education, the Bureau of Indian Affairs, problems of Native Americans on reservations, emergence of Native American militant groups, problems facing young Native Americans, working with Native American students, and Mr. Newmans work with Luisiano language.
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 41 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Whittier, California
- Laura Jean Scott, 1970 November 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1059)
- Henry Hale, 1970 November 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1060)
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Pico Rivera, California.
- James Quisquis and Mrs. James Quisquis, 1970 November 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1061)
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Buena Park, California
- Hotana Roebuck, 1970 December 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1062)
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Long Beach, California.
  Running Time: 45 minutes.
- Greta and Kenneth Yackitoonipah (Coman Che), 1970 November 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1063)
  Interviewed and recorded by Marian Ryan in Oklahoma
- Hannah Ortez, 1970 December 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1064)
  Interviewed and recorded by Marian Ryan in Fullerton, California
- Arthur Stoneking, 1971 March 20; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1065)
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Bell Gardens, California
- Delores Upshaw, 1971 March 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1066)
- Native American Children from Tuba City Boarding School, 1971 February 29; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1067)
  Various interviews with Native American children who attend the Tuba City Boarding School.
  Interviewed and recorded by Marion Ryan in Garden Grove, California
- Dr. Robert Delaney, 1971 August 19; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1068)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 41 minutes.
  interviewed and recorded by F. A. O'Neil and G. C. Thompson
- Margaret Campbell, 1971 July 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1069)
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 29 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Sharon Galassi in Riverside, California
- E.R. Smith, 1970 August 21; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1070)
  Alamitos intermediate School
- Benjamin Lee (Navajo), Virginia Anberson (Ute), 1971 May 26; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1071)
  Interviewed and recorded by Virginia Anderson in Salt Lake City
- Benjamin Lee (Navajo), 1971 March 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1072)
  Interviewed and recorded by C. G. Crampton in Salt Lake City, Utah.
- Ernie Peters (Souix), 1971 April 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1073)
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Valinda, California
- Iron Eyes Cody (Cherokee), 1971 April 06; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1074)
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Los Angeles, California
- A. David Lester, 1971 May 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1075)
  Interviewed and recorded by Nancy Callaci in Los Angeles, California
- Glover Young, 1971 April 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1076)
  Interviewed and recorded by C. Valenciana in La Mirada, California
- Margaret Thornburgh, 1971 May 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1077)
  Interviewed and recorded by C. Valenciana in Los Angeles, California
- Margaret Thornburgh, 1971 May 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1078)
  Interviewed and recorded by C. Valenciana
- Mr. Tom Knife Chief, 1971 10 May; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1079)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 49 minutes.
- Martina Casta-Cahuilla, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1080)
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Norwalk, California.
- Mrs. Judy Knife Chief, 1971 May 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1081)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 2 hr.
- Mrs. Judy Knife Chief, 1971 May 13; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1082)
- Edward Olivas, 1971 May 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1083)
  Interviewed and recorded by Nancy Callaci
- Larry J. Brown, 1971 April 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1084)
- Joe Yackytoonipah, 1970 December 16; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1085)
- Joe Yackytoonipah, 1970 November 06; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1086)
- Arlene Poemoceah, 1971 April 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1087)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 37 minutes.
  Side 1 follows side 2.
- Grace Jeppson, 1971 April 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1088)
- Helen Amgwerd, 1971 May 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1089)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 46 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by M. Ryan
- Elmer Poemoceah, 1970 December 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1090)
  Interviewed and recorded by G. Brown
- Carol Bowen, 1970 December 09; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1091)
  Interviewed and recorded by Kathy Biel in Corona, California
- Linda Rohrbach, 1971 January 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1092)
- Wayne Miller, 1970 November 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1093)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 1 hour 14 minutes.
- Lena Haberman, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1094)
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in La Mirada, California
- Wanda Bigcanoe Adamson, 1971 April 07; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1095)
  2 reel-to-reel audiotape, compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 2 hours 14 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Nancy Callaci in La Mirada, California.
- George Pierre, 1971 July 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1096)
  interviewed and recorded by May Jane DeCarlo in Whittier, California
- Carol Sue Tsosie (Navajo), undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1097)
- Glover Young, 1971 April 10; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1098)
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 42 minutes.
- Richard Gibbs, 1971 March 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1099)
  Interviewed and recorded by Christine Valenciana in Fullerton, California.
- Alex Lewis (Navajo), 1971 May 15; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1100)
  Alcohol problems.
  Side 2 precedes side 1.
- Thomasina Wermy, 1971 April 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1101)
  Running Time: 2 hrs 30 min
- Thomasina Wermy, 1971 Aprul 23; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1102)
- Leona Gabouri, 1971 April 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1103)
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Burbank, California
- Glover Young, 1971 April 27; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1104)
- Patricia Wills, 1971 May 02; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1105)
- Melvin Chiloquin, 1971 May 05; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1106)
  Available compact disc copy (1 CD) Total running time 2 hours 9 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by N. Callaci
- Mary Bitner (Arapahoe), 1971 April 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1107)
  Interviewed and recorded by Georgia Brown in Downey, California
- Natalie Rivera, 1971 March 22; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1108)
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 46 minutes.
- Ned Morgan (Navajo), 1971 June 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1109-I)
  Interviewed and recorded by J. D. Sylvester and Benjamin Lee.
- Ned Morgan (Navajo), 1971 June 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1109-II)
- Killian, Hooten, Osborne, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1110)
  Demography and the future of Man -
  Talks by: J. R. Killian, R. R. Hooten, and H. F. Osborne.
  Recorded for the Museum of N. Arizona Library Collection.
- Martin Link, 1971 July 06; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1111)
  Interviewed and recorded by J. D. Sylvester.
- Hodge Interviews, 1949; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1112)
  Recorded for the Museum of Northern Arizona Library Collection.
- Hohokam Irrigation Lecture, undated; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1113)
  Hohokam Irrigation.
- Mike Zuni (Navajo), 1971 June 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1114-I)
  Translation of original interview
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour minutes.
- Mike Zuni (Navajo), 1971 June 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1114-II)
- Akejibah Zuni (Navajo), 1971 June 30; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1115)
  Navajo Claims
  Interviewed and recorded by Benjamin Lee.
- Peter Yazza (Navajo), 1971 July 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1116)
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow
- Peter Yazza (Navajo), 1971 July 08; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1117)
- Glenmae Tsosie, 1971 July 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1118-I)
  Available compact disc copy (3 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 56 minutes.
  Interviewed and recorded by Benjamin Lee and Virginia Anderson for the Tribal Museum of Arizona.
- Glenmae Tsosie, 1971 July 12; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1118-II)
  Available compact disc copy (2 CDs) Total running time 1 hour 27 minutes.
- Charlie Sam, 1971 June 28; Reel-to-reel audiotape (Reel 1119-I)
  Interviewed and recorded by E. Bulow and M. Metteba.